bountifulbaskets.org 2018-12-16

# Privacy Policy « Bountiful Baskets

**Privacy Policy**

Welcome to the Bountiful Baskets Website!  By using our “Site” (www.bountifulbaskets.org) and our services (“Bountiful Baskets”), you consent to the collection and use of information you submit as described in this Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy serves as an agreement between Bountiful Baskets  (“BB”) and any person or business (each a “User” or “Participant”) that visits the Site or accesses or participates in the Bountiful Baskets. “We” are BB and “You” are the “User” or “Participant.”

**“Personal information”**  is data about an individual who can be identified from that data, or from that data and other information to which onehasaccess.  Personal Information is usually your name in combination with another identifier, such as date of birth, postal address, email address, telephone number, or government-issued identification number. The specific definition of Personal Information often varies from one jurisdiction to another.

**What Personal Information Do We Collect?**

When you contact us or participate in a group purchase using the Bountiful Baskets, we may collect a variety of personal information, including your name, mailing address, phone number, email address and contact preferences.

**How Do We Use Your Personal Information?**

We may use your Personal Information to identify you; to track your use of the Site or activity with a Bountiful Baskets location; to assess your degree of satisfaction with the Bountiful Baskets or the Site; to update you about Bountiful Baskets; to improve the effectiveness of the Site or Bountiful Baskets; to prevent, deter and investigate violations of this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, or any fraud and other illegal activities; and to send you important notices regarding Bountiful Baskets.

**With Whom Do We Share Your Personal Information?**

We may share your Personal Information with third parties who may help us operate the Site or help us assess your interest or satisfaction with the Site or the Bountiful Baskets.

We may disclose your Personal Information if we determine that disclosure is reasonably necessary to enforce our Terms of Use, this Privacy Policy or to otherwise protect our operations, participants or users.

We may release your Personal Information to others (including law enforcement) if we believe such release is reasonably necessary to comply with the law or legal process; enforce or apply the terms of applicable terms of use; detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues; or otherwise protect the rights, property or safety of others.

**How Do We Protect Your Personal Information?**

We maintain a variety of security measures, including physical, electronic and procedural safeguards.  No system can be completely secure, so we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your Personal Information, searches, or other communications will always remain secure.

**Your Access to Personal Information**

You may log into your account and check your Personal Information so that you can determine if it is accurate or if it needs to be updated.  If you want it deleted, provided we not required to retain it by law or for legitimate business purposes, and we will complete your request as time allows.

We may decline to process requests that are frivolous/vexatious, jeopardize the privacy of others, are extremely impractical, or for which access is not otherwise required by local law. Deletion requests can be made to TanyaandSally@BountifulBaskets.org

**What Other Information Do We Collect?**

We automatically gather information when you browse or view the Site. This log data may include your browser type (e.g., Chrome, Safari, Firefox or Internet Explorer), your domain, the Internet Protocol (IP) address assigned to your computer (or the unique device ID of your mobile device, or other unique identifier), the date and time of your visits, the pages on the Site you visit and other information related to your visit.  We do not, however, use cookies on our Site.

You should be able to manage how your browser and mobile device shares share information about your visits by adjusting your browser or device’s privacy and security settings.

We collect data that does not, on its own, permit direct association with any specific individual. We may collect, use, transfer, and disclose such non-personal information for any purpose.  If we combine non-personal information with your Personal Information, we will maintain the combined information as Personal Information for as long as it remains combined.

There are “do not track” or similar browser choices available to internet users with respect to online web activity, but given the present lack of consensus of what constitutes an informed election, appropriate trigger or breadth of scope of such choice, the Site will not operate any differently when a “do not track” signal is received.

**Social Networking Sites**

You may be able to post content to Social Networking Sites (such as Facebook, Instagram, Snapchat or Twitter) on which we maintain a presence.  If you choose to do this, we will provide information to the Social Networking Sites in accordance with your elections.  You acknowledge and agree that you are solely responsible for your use of those Sites and that it is your responsibility to review the terms of use and privacy policies.  We are not responsible for the availability, accuracy, content, products or services of such Social Network Sites.

**Third Party Links**

The Site may have links or be linked to other sites we do not own, control or maintain. We are not responsible for and make no representations or warranties about the privacy practices of those sites. We recommend that you check the privacy policies of other sites and contact the operator if you have concerns or questions. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of the Site and welcome any feedback about these third party sites.

**Children**

The Site is not directed to minors.  If we learn that we have collected personal information from anyone under the age of 13, we will try to delete such information as soon as reasonably possible.

**Privacy Rights of California Residents**

California residents are entitled once a year, free of charge, to request and obtain certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes.   _We do not disclose personal information to third parties for direct marketing purposes._

**Changes to our Privacy Statement**

We may update this Privacy Statement from time to time, so please check the effective date at the top of this page as the date of last revision. Changes will become immediately effective upon posting on the Site unless otherwise noted.  Your use of the Site following these changes indicates your consent to the practices described in the revised Privacy Statement.

Last revised: May 31, 2018
